hey everyone welcome to my channel i am with you nitin pal and you are watching insurance guru
friends as you all know from 1st january 2023 it is necessary to do KYC on renewal or fresh policies of all insurances
friends in today's video I will tell you that when you
underwrite a policy on the portal of United India Insurance, then
how to do C KYC in it, then friends, customers who already have C KYC, if you fill their C KYC number
in the insurance policy, then you will get a new C KYC. There will be no need to do the same C KYC is a 14 digital
numeric number, so friends, customers who already have C KYC number,
you can renew their policy by filling their C KYC number in the insurance policy or issue a fresh policy. If you can
, then you can also fill C KYC in the customer ID in the portal of Friends United Insurance, you can fill
C KYC number even while unwriting the policy, and if someone does not have C KYC number
, then how to do his C KYC today's v I will tell you this in Dio, friends, now you
are watching the picture in your mobile or on your computer, in this the screenshot has been shared with
you, in this you will see that when we do the Android policy, then along with filling the details of the customer
There is an option to fill a KYC number as well, if a customer has a KYC number, then here he
has to fill 14 digits and friends, now you are seeing the screenshot on your screen, this
is the time of creating a new customer ID. Here, when you create a new customer ID,
you can fill the C KYC number here as well or if you are already a customer, then by modifying the customer ID,
you can update the customer in any KYC United India Insurance policy by filling the C KYC number. So friends now further I will
tell you how to do fresh KYC of customers who do not have C KYC number then friends
when you normally android a policy you know all the steps to unwrite the policy like you
android a policy How to end the insurance policy After that you will get
the payment options in the last one, there will be an error that the customer has not updated any KYC, then
first of all you have to update the KYC, then in the case of friends, the registered mobile number of the customer will be
a link on it. It will go, you have to click on the link and follow the instructions. The KYC
link will go to the customer care register number only, then the link that will go to the register number
, when you open the link, it will be the first link in the link. C KYC is to be done for the customer whose name is the vehicle
, he will have to upload his selfie, he will be given four or five types of documents in the link, gym passport,
driving license, van side driving license, two side Aadhaar card or Boat Riddhi card
, option of these documents. If you get to see any of these documents
, you have to update them in the link, then the documents mentioned in the link of Friends C KYC will
be available with the customer when the customer uploads the document on the link of C KYC. will give
and up will upload the selfie then he will get a message saying thank you for confirming your done
so friends this way the customer's KYC will be done then when you pay for the customer's policy
then after the KYC is done the payment for the customer's policy will be done Friends, this was today's video in which I told you
that from January 1, 2023,
C KYC is necessary to buy a new insurance policy or to renew the old policy, the customer whose C is the same
They only have to provide their C KYC number and those who do not have it, they
will have to do new C KYC, so friends, how did you like today's video, you will definitely tell me in the comment section, related to this video
related to insurance or related to you from there. If you want to ask anything then you can also ask me
in the comment section, that's it for today, see you soon with a new video, Jai Hind Jai Bharat